The word world is not a bad place?
The word world is...
I'm the type of person who shuts up.
I'm the type of person who says, "Bread, that's enough.
I've had enough for today.
But when I have a day off...
I'm pretty much mainly doing 00.
In this year's horoscope book
It says that it's good to do 00.
And it also says that you two have a part in it?
I saw that moment.
You saw it?
You came to the project to give a class.
I met you there for the first time.
Yes, thank you. I'm Mr. Yoru, the middle quality education teacher at Sturzast.
I would like to call today's guest.
This is Mr. Idol here. Please come in.
Yes, I'm Director Murahoshi of Ukka. I am Director Murahoshi of Ukka. Pleased to meet you.
Yes. I am pleased to welcome Mr. Muraboshi, Director of Ukka.
I look forward to working with you.
I know you have been on the nightly titles for a long time now,
How is it going? Have you become closer to Daikoku Land?
Yes, we have. Yuzuki-chan and I had a chance to talk with each other,
We had a lot in common,
She suggested that we go to Sanryo Puroland together,
I would like to go there next time. We have a promise.
Yes. You mean Puroland.
Did you get any reaction from fans after watching the video?
Yes, I have. It was really the first time for me to talk with Yuzuki,That's right. It was really the first time for me to have a conversation with Yuzuki-chan,
It was the first time for the two of us to talk together,
So it was fresh and fun,
I was happy that Yuzuki and I could get along so well,
I was happy that Yuzuki and I were able to become good friends through this opportunity.
Who initiated the idea of going to Puro Land?
Yuzuki-chan was the one who suggested it,
I was thinking of Sanryo's character,
I like Pom Pom Pudding,
Yuzuki-chan likes Cinnamoroll.
So, when we were able to perform at each other's shows, we were very happy to see the characters we both liked,
We started talking about how happy we were to meet each other's favorite characters,
Yuzuki-chan suggested that we go to Puroland next time.
I see.
This is a totally different story,
I don't mean to change the subject at all, but...,
There is a character announcement for Sanryo every year, isn't there?
Yes, there is. Yes, there is.
Do you worry about the popularity of the character you guessed?
Yes, but my guess is Pom Pom Pudding,
He's unquestionably No. 2.
I know, right?
And Cinnamoroll is No. 1.
The turnip ranking has not changed,
I don't really want to be No. 1, but...,
But there is a poll on the web, so I'm going to vote for it once.
So you're a bit of a charlatan, aren't you?
I see. Thank you very much.
But next year seems to be Kitty's anniversary,
There are rumors that Kitty will be number one next year.There are rumors that Kitty will be the number one next year.
Kitty is expected to be No. 1 next year.
Also, Kuromi-chan is also said to be coming quite a bit.
That's right. She is in the third place every year, isn't she?
Yes, she does.
I see.
Then, next year, I'd like to aim for first place,
I hope you will mount Mr. Oura with Pom Pom Pudding.
Thank you very much.
I'm so good at making progress that I'm ahead of the rest of my friends.
This program is
Rui-san
Ryo-san
Naoki Star
Kodeie-san
Chia-chan provided this program!
Thank you for your contribution!